<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Insurance</string>
	<string name="CreateStatement">Dont have an account ? create new</string>
	<string name="WelCome">Welcome !</string>
	<string name="LoginContinue">Please login to continue</string>
	<string name="signupContinue">Please sign up to continue</string>
	<string name="otp">Please Verify yout Register \n mobile number</string>
	<string name="Hey">Hey !</string>
	<string name="Resend">We just Sent you OTP to your register \n register mobile number or Resend</string>
	<string name="agent">I am Insurance Agent</string>
	<string name="title_activity_home_screen">HomeScreenActivity</string>
	<string name="FindDetails">Find Details</string>
	<string name="INSURANCE">INSURANCE</string>
	<string name="option">We will help you to find the best auto insurance \n option in your area</string>
	<string name="Get">Get Details</string>
	<string name="EnterNo">Enter Registration number [Ex: KA01EF72727]</string>
	<string name="owner">Owner</string>
	<string name="makeyear">Make Year</string>
	<string name="address">Address</string>
	<string name="Chaisino">Chasi No</string>
	<string name="Engno">Eng No</string>
	<string name="Idv">IDV Value</string>
	<string name="PreviuosPolicy">Previous Policy</string>
	<string name="insuranceto">Insurance To</string>
	<string name="insuranceFrom">Insurance from</string>
	<string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
	<string name="Congratulations">Congratulations !</string>
	<string name="GoToMyInsurance">Go To My Insurance</string>
	<string name="DetailPrevious">Details Previous Policy</string>

	<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
	<string name="Requestsurveyer">Request for surveyer</string>
	<string name="AddPhoto">Add photo</string>
	<string name="uploadPolicy">Upload Policy Document</string>
	<string name="proceedTo">Proceed To Insurance</string>
	<string name="EnterPrevious">Enter Previous Policy Number(Optional)</string>
	<string name="title_activity_insurance_details">InsuranceDetailsActivity</string>
	<string name="Myinsurance">My Insurance</string>
	<string name="ExpiryDate">Expiry Date</string>
	<string name="StartDate">Start Date</string>
	<string name="PolicyNo">Policy No</string>
	<string name="IdvT">IDV</string>
	<string name="product">Product</string>
	<string name="Ncb">NCB</string>
	<string name="InsurancePlan">Insurance Plan</string>
	<string name="Inusurance">Inusurance</string>
	<string name="things">Things covered by insurance</string>
	<string name="vehicle">Vehicle</string>
	<string name="price">Price</string>
	<string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
	<string name="EnterOTP">Please enter 5 digit OTP</string>
	<string name="AddNominee">Add Nominee</string>
	<string name="EnterName">Enter Name of Nominee*</string>
	<string name="EnterNominee">Enter Relation with Nominee*</string>
	<string name="Next">Next</string>
	<string name="payHere">Pay Now</string>
	<string name="Total">Total</string>
	<string name="upload_rc_book">Upload RC book</string>
	<string name="upload_address_proof">Upload address proof</string>
	<string name="upload_id_proof">Upload id proof</string>
	<string name="policy">Policy</string>
	<string name="rc">RC</string>
	<string name="id">ID</string>
	<string name="selectvechiletype">Select Vehicle Type</string>
	<string name="termscondition"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
	<string name="claimtext">Are you sure, you have not claimed any insurance in your last premium?</string>
	<string name="claimtextnext">n your insurance will be revoked case we find any claim than you are not eligible for an insurance.</string>
	<string name="addvehiclephote">Upload Vehicle Photo</string>
	<string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
	<string name="aboutusdesc">We are pioneer in the segment of general insurance renewable business to avoid complexity and lengthy process to renew the vehicle insurance policy,  we have created easy and user friendly app to renew the policy in just 5 simple steps also we have provided flexibility to search vehicle detail by just feeding vehicle number with the flexibility of online payment and instance policy issuance solution.</string>

	<string name="termsncondition">Terms and Condition</string>
	<string name="policydesc">incorrect information or mismatch in the detail policy will not be issued.\nPolicy  will be
        issued post receiving the payment.\nPolicy renewal should be done 24 hours before the policy expiry date.\nKarnataka (bangalore) jurisdiction only.\nAll right reserved</string>
	<string name="EnterAgentNumber">Enter Agent number(Optional)</string>
	<string name="forsmartcoveragency">For smart cover Agent only</string>
	<string name="youaredone">You are done</string>
	<string name="pleasewait">Please wait...</string>


	<string name="upload_activity">UploadActivity</string>
	<string name="download_activity">DownloadActivity</string>
	<string name="download_selection_activity">Select a file from the bucket</string>
	<string name="download">Download</string>
	<string name="manage_download">Manage downloads</string>
	<string name="manage_upload">Manage uploads</string>
	<string name="upload">Upload</string>
	<string name="upload_file">Upload a file</string>
	<string name="upload_image">Upload an image</string>
	<string name="pause">Pause</string>
	<string name="resume">Resume</string>
	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
	<string name="delete">Delete</string>
	<string name="pause_all">Pause all</string>
	<string name="cancel_all">Cancel all</string>
	<string name="refreshing">Refreshing</string>
	<string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
	<string name="uploadingdocuments">Please wait, while we Upload Documents</string>
	<string name="policydocument">policyDocument</string>
	<string name="rcbook">RcBook</string>
	<string name="addressproof">AddressProof</string>
	<string name="idproof">IdProof</string>

	<string name="privacypolicy"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Privacy Policy:</strong></p>
<p>The domain name bookmyinsurance.co.in (hereinafter referred to as "Website/App") is owned by Rajachan Advisors Private Limited company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 with its registered office at World Trade Centre, 22nd Floor, Unit No 2201A, No. 26/1 Dr. Raj Kumar Road, Brigade Gateway Campus, Malleswaram, Bangalore 560055, Karnataka, India (hereinafter referred to as "bookmyinsurance.co.in").<br /><br />By using the website/app and/or registering yourself at BookMyInsurance.co.in you authorize us, our affiliates &amp; our associate partners to contact you via email or phone call or sms and offer you their services for the product you have opted for, imparting product knowledge, offer promotional offers running on website &amp; offers offered by the associated third parties, for which reasons, as well as web aggregation, personally identifiable information may be collected as detailed below. And Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC or NCPR service, you still authorize us to give you a call from the BookMyInsurance &amp; associate partners for the above mentioned purposes till 45 days of your registration with us. This Privacy Policy covers BookMyInsurance\'s treatment of personally identifiable information that BookMyInsurance collects when you are on the BookMyInsurance site, and when you use BookMyInsurance\'s services. This policy also covers BookMyInsurance\'s treatment of any personally identifiable information that BookMyInsurance\'s business partners share with BookMyInsurance. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BookMyInsurance does not own or control or to people that BookMyInsurance does not employ or manage. BookMyInsurance collects personally identifiable information when you register for a BookMyInsurance account, when you use certain BookMyInsurance products or services, when you visit BookMyInsurance pages, and when you enter promotions. BookMyInsurance may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.<br /><br />When you register with BookMyInsurance, we ask for your first name, last name, state, city, email, birth date, and gender. Once you register with BookMyInsurance and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Also during registration, you may be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, pager, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorize us to send sms/email alerts to you for your login details and any other service requirements or some advertising messages/emails from us.</p>
<p>Information Sharing and Disclosure BookMyInsurance will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone other than as specifically noted herein. Notwithstanding the foregoing, BookMyInsurance may share, sell and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to an affiliate and/or associate partner/business partner. BookMyInsurance may also share, sell, and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of BookMyInsurance\'s business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of BookMyInsurance with another entity on a basis that BookMyInsurance is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this paragraph, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with BookMyInsurance. The term "control," as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "person" includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, limited liability company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity."If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, or you want us to remove any PII that we have collected about you, please e-mail your request to support@bookmyinsurance.co.in."</p>
<p>Third Party Advertising We may use third-party advertising companies and/or ad agencies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (excluding your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you."We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.""If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click here. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative,s website by clicking here."</p>
<p><u><strong>Legal</strong></u></p>
<p>We strictly follow the norms of non disclosure and any agreement thereof. It is our endeavour to ensure that the websites linked to us are safe and secure. However we have no control over 3rd party websites. Given our legal responsibilities to legal authorities and regulators, there may be situations when we need to share your information with legal authorities or processes or need to protect our right or comply by terms and conditions.</p>
<p><u><strong>Other sites</strong></u></p>
<p>There might be affiliates or other sites linked to our web site. Personal information that you provide to those sites are not our property. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. These sites may place their cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.</p>
<p><u><strong>Privacy Policy Changes</strong></u><br /><br />BookMyInsurance may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages.</p>
<p>Associate Partners for vehicle Insurance - Reliance Vehicle Insurance Company Limited<br /><br /><u><strong>Disclaimer</strong></u></p>
<p>Visitors to this website/portal and every third party is hereby informed that the owners of this website/portal, viz Rajachan Advisors Private Limited ., are not the agents or intermediaries of the insurers, whose products are dealt with in this website/portal. They are also not the sub-agents or sub-intermediaries of the agents and intermediaries of the respective insurers. Though endeavour is made to make correct policy/product comparisons, quotes, features, etc., based on the information provided by the insurers or its agents or intermediaries, it is made abundantly clear that Rajachan Advisors Private Limited ., its directors, shareholders, officers and employees and BookMyInsurance.co.in are in no way responsible to or liable for any one for his/her investment decision, and every prospect/ investor/policyholder shall be solely responsible for the consequences of his/her decision. Not-withstanding anything mentioned before, we reserve the right to contact you via any mechanisms, not limited to email, sms, or phone calls, to solicit feedback of your experience and to provide any additional services that you would be eligible for, either as a customer or as a visitor. We are not liable for any damages occurring to you as part of feedback solicitation and additional service provision."We use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and clear gifs to store certain types of information each time you visit any page on our website. Cookies enable this website to recognize the information you have consented to give to this website and help us determine what portions of this website are most appropriate for your professional needs. We may also use cookies to serve advertising banners to you. These banners may be served by us or by a third party on our behalf. These cookies will not contain any personal information.""Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven\'t changed your computer\'s settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies of disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on."</p>
<p><u><strong>Intellectual Property</strong></u></p>
<p><strong>Rajachan Advisors Private Limited</strong> (the "Company") has an efficient Intellectual Property Policy and Intellectual Property Management guidelines (Collectively referred to as "IP Policy", hereinafter) in place basically to maintain absolute clarity on IPR related issues such as ownership, rights and obligation of employees and Company, rights and obligation of customers and Company, disclosure of work/ invention, non-disclosure of confidential information, liabilities in case of misappropriation of IP or resolution of IP related disputes strategically.</p>
<p>Intellectual property IP is one of our most valuable assets. We rely on various types of intellectual property (such
    as trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets, domain names, design rights) for our success in the market. IP
    helps us stay competitive, allows us to fund future successes, and supports each of our jobs at the Company. The
    Company has a consistent policy of identification of Company\'s intangible assets, prioritizing them according to
    Company\'s business plans, registering, exploiting and safeguarding them in order to benefit fully from IP in terms
    of revenue, reputation and market share. The Company\'s IP Policy also envisages protection and management of its own IP well, internally and with it\'s business partners. We also want to respect the IP of others as we develop our products and services, run our business, and work with business partners.</p>
<p>For clarifications, the term Company wherever used under this IP policy, shall include its Subsidiaries and Affiliates.</p>
<p><strong>PURPOSE</strong></p>
<p><br />The Company has adopted this Policy in order to protect its own IP and minimize the possibility of infringement of Intellectual Property rights of the Company and the third Parties. This IP Policy aims to provide transparent administrative system for the ownership, control and transfer of the IP created and owned by the Company.</p>
<p><strong>APPLICABILITY</strong></p>
<p>This IP Policy is applicable to all the employees, representatives and agents of the Company including its Subsidiaries and Affiliates.</p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><strong>POLICIES, PROCEDURES, AND RECORDS</strong></p>
<p>Company shall respect intellectual property (IP) and conduct its business in compliance with the IP-related laws as applicable in the jurisdiction of Republic of India and its agreements with other companies.</p>
<p>Company shall actively protect its own IP.</p>
<p>Company shall maintain an effective system of IP asset management, including maintaining an inventory and records of IP-related assets and agreements.</p>
<p>Company shall not knowingly infringe a third party\'s intellectual property in its products, services, or components,
    or disclose or use a third party\'s trade secrets without the express or implied consent of the owner or as permitted by law.</p>
<p>Company shall not knowingly purchase or use counterfeit or other infringing goods and services in running its business, including counterfeit trademark goods or infringing copyright material (such as software, publications, video, audio, or other content).</p>
<p>Company shall document and maintain written records of all substantial transactions and uses that involve the exercise of IP rights. (This includes, for example, licenses or assignments of rights; manufacture, reproduction or distribution of patented, trademarked or copyrighted items; and disclosure and use of trade secrets.)</p>
<p>Company shall require, through binding policies or agreements with employees and contractors that its personnel comply
    with the applicable IP laws and the Company\'s IP policies and IP-related provisions in agreements with other
    companies.</p>
<p>Company shall develop and implement a management system to help ensure that all personnel follow its IP policies. This
    management system shall encompass all IP-related policies, procedures and adequate and accurate records necessary to
    implement, measure, and improve Company\'s IP protection and compliance program.</p>
<p><strong>IP COMPLIANCE TEAM</strong></p>
<p>Company\'s IP protection and management shall be implemented through a cross-functional compliance team, overseen by a
    Director or CFO of the Company or designated senior management. The said compliance team may appoint or engage any advocate or expert from within and/or outside the Company to seek their opinion in carrying out their responsibilities as stated under this IP Policy.</p>
<p>SCOPE AND QUALITY OF RISK ASSESSMENT</p>
<p>Company shall include in its risk assessment of new products, services, and business opportunities, any relevant IP protection risks.</p>
<p>MANAGEMENT OF BUSINESS PARTNERS:</p>
<p>Company shall require its business partners to conduct their arrangements with the Company in accordance with
    Company\'s relevant IP protection policies.</p>
<p>Company shall conduct initial risk assessment and due diligence on all prospective business partners, which shall
    include an assessment of such companies\' IP protection and management.</p>
<p>SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY MANAGEMENT</p>
<p>Company shall maintain physical security designed to effectively protect trade secrets (where applicable) and other confidential information, and IP-related records, masters, tools, inventory and related materials.</p>
<p>Company shall maintain computer and network security effective for protecting trade secrets, other confidential and
    proprietary information, and IP related records, and for discouraging violations of Company\'s IP policies on the
    Company\'s computers and networks.</p>
<p>Company and its personnel shall only make trade secrets and other proprietary information available to third parties on a "need to know" basis, and subject to company procedures and written agreements containing adequate confidentiality and other protections.</p>
<p>Company shall execute written confidential or Non-disclosure agreements with third parties prior to disclosure of any confidential information of the Company to any third party (ies).</p>
<p>Any IP generated, created or developed by any of the employees/representatives and agents of the Company and/or consultants engaged by the Company, during the term of their employment or engagement as the case may be, for and/or on behalf of the Company, shall be "work made for hire" and shall be assigned by such persons to the Company. Further, the Company shall have the sole and exclusive ownership to such IP generated, developed or created unless otherwise agreed by the Company by way of a written contract or as may be applicable by the relevant IP law.</p>
<p>TRAINING AND CAPACITY BUILDING</p>
<p>Company shall provide ongoing appropriate level training on IP protection and management to all relevant personnel.</p>
<p>Company shall provide specialized training to those personnel responsible for the development and implementation of the IP protection, management, and compliance program.</p>
<p>Company shall provide appropriate level training on IP protection and management for relevant supply chain members.</p>
<p>MONITORING AND MEASUREMENT</p>
<p>Company shall establish and operate a system to monitor its performance in meeting the Company\'s relevant IP
    policies.</p>
<p>Company shall incorporate the information gained from the IP compliance team through the monitoring system into the overall evaluation of its departments.</p>
<p>CORRECTIVE ACTIONS AND IMPROVEMENTS:</p>
<p>Company shall maintain a system to track and deal with problems in IP protection, management and compliance found through the monitoring process. The tracking system will identify the corrective action to be taken, the timeline, and the responsible party.</p>
<p><br />Company shall develop and implement an annual or other regular improvement plan for IP protection, management, and compliance.</p>
<p>In case of violation/infringement of any IPR such as trademark infringement by any employee/representative or any third party infringing upon the IPR of the Company, the Compliance Team of the Company would first investigate the matter in association with its Advocates and make recommendations to the Director/CFO for resolution of such violation/infringement including need for any legal course of action.</p>
<p>IP Licensing and Transfer</p>
<p>The Company may license its IP to any of its Subsidiaries, Affiliates or a third party (ies) through various modes of licensing strategy such as: Exclusive licensing, Sole licensing, Non-Exclusive Licensing, Sub-licensing and licensing in general. The Company shall document such IP licensing through a license Agreement where each such license agreement shall define the terms and conditions for the proper use of IP of the Company.</p>
<p>The Company may transfer its IP to any of its Subsidiaries, Affiliates or a third party (ies) through a signed IP transfer agreement on the conditions as may be deemed to be fit and proper to the Company.</p>
<p>Jurisdiction</p>
<p>This Policy shall be governed by the laws of Republic of India and the courts at Bangalore, Karnataka shall have the jurisdiction to the same.</p>
<p><strong>Your Consent</strong></p>
<p>By using the Website/App and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.</p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p>If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.</p>
<p><strong>Grievance Officer</strong></p>
<p>In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:</p>
<p>Mr. Srinivasa Rao</p>
<p>Rajachan Advisors Private Limited</p>
<p>World Trade Centre, 22nd Floor, Unit No 2201A, No. 26/1 Dr. Raj Kumar Road, Brigade Gateway Campus, Malleswaram, Bangalore 560055</p>
<p>Phone: 080-67935879</p>
<p>Email: grievance.officer@bookmyinsurance.co.in</p>
<p>Time: Mon - Sat (9:00 - 18:00)</p>
<p>Questions?</p>
<p>Please contact us regarding any questions regarding this statement.</p>]]></string>

	<string name="termsconditiondesc"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Terms:</strong></p>
<p>The domain name bookmyinsurance.co.in (hereinafter referred to as "Website/App") is owned by Rajachan Advisors Private Limited company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 with its registered office at World Trade Centre, 22nd Floor, Unit No 2201A, No. 26/1 Dr. Raj Kumar Road, Brigade Gateway Campus, Malleswaram, Bangalore 560055, Karnataka, India (hereinafter referred to as "bookmyinsurance.co.in").<br /><br />Welcome to www.BookMyInsurance.co.in website (the "Site") and app operated by Rajachan Advisors Private Limited). BookMyInsurance provides its services to you subject to the following conditions. Before you may use the Site, you must read and accept all of the terms and conditions in, and linked to, this Terms of Use and the linked Privacy Policy. We strongly recommend that, as you read this ToU, you also access and read the linked information, since it is incorporated into and hereby made part of this ToU. This ToU is effective upon acceptance. Use of any functionality of the Site constitutes acceptance of this ToU. If this ToU conflicts with any other documents, the ToU will control for the purposes of usage of the Site. If you do not agree to be bound by this ToU and the Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site in any way. Be sure to return to this page periodically to review the most current version of the ToU. We reserve the right, at any time, at our sole discretion, to change or otherwise modify the TOU without prior notice, and your continued access or use of this Site signifies your acceptance of the updated or modified TOU.</p>
<p>1. Description of Services</p>
<p>In the Site, BookMyInsurance provides users with access to information primarily about Financial and Insurance products and services including but not restricted to General Insurance, Life Insurance products and related services (including but not limited to renewals) (the "Service"). You are responsible for obtaining access to the Site, and that access may involve third-party fees (such as Internet service provider or airtime charges). In addition, you must provide and are responsible for all equipment necessary to access the Site. By making use of this site, and furnishing your personal / contact details, you hereby agree that you are interested in availing and purchasing the Service(s) that you have selected. You hereby agree that BookMyInsurance may contact you either electronically or through phone, to understand your interest in the selected products and Service(s) (like renewals, reminders etc.) and to fulfill your demand. You also agree that BookMyInsurance reserves the right to make your details available to its affiliates and partners and you may be contacted by the affiliates and partners for information and for sales through email, telephone and/or sms. You agree to receive promotional materials and/or special offers from BookMyInsurance through email or sms.</p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><strong>2. License and Site Access</strong></p>
<p>BookMyInsurance grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of the Site/App and the Service. This license does not include any downloading or copying of any kind of information for the benefit of another individual, vendor or any other third party; caching, unauthorized hypertext links to the Site and the framing of any Content available through the Site uploading, posting, or transmitting any content that you do not have a right to make available (such as the intellectual property of another party); uploading, posting, or transmitting any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; any action that imposes or may impose (in BookMyInsurance\'s sole discretion) an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on BookMyInsurance\'s infrastructure; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. You may not bypass any measures used by BookMyInsurance to prevent or restrict access to the Site. Any unauthorized use by you shall terminate the permission or license granted to you by BookMyInsurance. By using the Site you agree not to: (i) use this Site or its contents for any commercial purpose; (ii) make any speculative, false, or fraudulent transaction or any transaction in anticipation of demand; (iii) access, monitor or copy any content or information of this Site using any robot, spider, scraper or other automated means or any manual process for any purpose without our express written permission; (iv) violate the restrictions in any robot exclusion headers on this Site or bypass or circumvent other measures employed to prevent or limit access to this Site; (v) take any action that imposes, or may impose, in our discretion, an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure; (vi) deep-link to any portion of this Site (including, without limitation, the purchase path for any service) for any purpose without our express written permission; or (vii) "frame", "mirror" or otherwise incorporate any part of this Site into any other website without our prior written authorization.</p>
<p><strong>3. Eligibility</strong></p>
<p>The Service is not available to minors under the age of 18 or to any users suspended or removed from the system by BookMyInsurance for any reason. Users may not have more than one active account. Additionally, users are prohibited from selling, trading, or otherwise transferring their accounts to another party. If you do not qualify, you may not use the Service or the Site.</p>
<p><strong>4. Your Account</strong></p>
<p>In consideration of your use of the Site, you represent that you are of legal age to form a binding contract and are not a person barred from receiving services under the laws of India or other applicable jurisdiction and will only use the Site to make legitimate purchases for you or for another person for whom you are legally authorized to act (and will inform such other persons about the ToU and/or Privacy Policy) that apply to the purchase you have made on their behalf (including all rules and restrictions applicable thereto). You also agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the Site. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete (or becomes untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete), or BookMyInsurance has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, BookMyInsurance has the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the Site (or any portion thereof). If you use the Site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, and for restricting access to your computer. You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. Because of this, we strongly recommend that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You agree to notify BookMyInsurance immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. BookMyInsurance reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, or remove or edit content in its sole discretion. Notwithstanding the above, we retain the right at our sole discretion to deny access to anyone to the Site and the Services we offer, at any time and for any reason, including, but not limited to, for violation of the ToU or Privacy Policy. Additional terms and conditions will apply to your purchase of Services that you select. Please read these additional terms and conditions carefully. You agree to abide by the terms and conditions of purchase imposed by any service provider with whom you elect to deal, including, but not limited to, payment of all amounts when due and compliance with the service provider\'s rules and restrictions regarding use of products, and/or Services. You agree that any violation of any such service provider\'s rules and restrictions may result in cancellation of your purchase(s), in your being denied access to the applicable service(s), in your forfeiting any monies paid for such Services, and/or in our debiting your account for any costs we incur as a result of such violation.</p>
<p><strong>5. Submitted Content</strong></p>
<p>BookMyInsurance does not claim ownership of any materials you make available through the Site. At BookMyInsurance\'s sole discretion, such materials may be included in the Service in whole or in part or in a modified form. With respect to such materials you submit or make available for inclusion on the Site, you grant BookMyInsurance a perpetual, irrevocable, non-terminable, worldwide, royalty-free and non-exclusive license to use, copy, distribute, publicly display, modify, create derivative works, and sublicense such materials or any part of such materials (as well as use the name that you submit in connection with such submitted content). You hereby represent, warrant and covenant that any materials you provide do not include anything (including, but not limited to, text, images, music or video) to which you do not have the full right to grant the license specified in this Section 4. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any submitted content posted or submitted by you. We have no obligation to post your comments; we reserve the right in our absolute discretion to determine which comments are published on the Site. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not provide us with any submitted content. You agree that you are fully responsible for the content you submit. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Site: (i) any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or other material or content that would violate rights of publicity and/or privacy or that would violate any law; (ii) any commercial material or content (including, but not limited to, solicitation of funds, advertising, or marketing of any good or services); and (iii) any material or content that infringes, misappropriates or violates any copyright, trademark, patent right or other proprietary right of any third party. You shall be solely liable for any damages resulting from any violation of the foregoing restrictions, or any other harm resulting from your posting of content to this Site.</p>
<p><strong>6. Disclaimer of Liability and Warranty</strong></p>
<p>The Content, Products, and Services Published on this site may include inaccuracies or errors, Including Pricing errors. We do not guarantee the accuracy of , and disclaim all liability for any errors or other inaccuracies relating to the information and description of the content, products, and services we expressly reserves the right to correct any pricing errors on the site and/or on pending reservations made under an incorrect price. BookMyInsurance makes no representation about the suitability of the information, Software, products, and services contained on this site for any purpose, and the inclusion or offering of any products or services on this site does not constitute any endorsement or recommendation of such products or services. All such information, software, products, and services are provided "AS IS" without warranty of any kind. BookMyInsurance disclaims all warranties and conditions that this site, its services or any email sent from BookMyInsurance, its affiliates, and/or their respective or associated service providers are free of viruses or other harmful components. BookMyInsurance hereby disclaims all warranties and conditions with regard to this information, software, products, and services, including all implied warranties and conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and no infringement. The service providers providing services on this site are independent affiliates and BookMyInsurance are not liable for the acts, errors, omissions, representations, warranties, breaches or negligence of any such service providers or for any personal injuries, death, property damage, or other damages or expenses resulting therefore. BookMyInsurance and its affiliates have no liability and will make no refund in the event of any delay, cancellation, strike, force majeure or other causes beyond their direct control, and they have no responsibility for any additional expense omissions delays or acts of any government or authority. In no event shall BookMyInsurance and/or its affiliates be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of, or in any way connected with, your access to, display of or use of this site or with the delay or inability to access, display or use this site (including, but not limited to, your reliance upon opinions appearing on this site; any computer viruses, information, software, linked sites, products, and services obtained through this site; or otherwise arising out of the access to, display of or use of this site) whether based on a theory of negligence, contract, tort, strict liability, or otherwise, and even if BookMyInsurance and/or its affiliates their respective service providers have been advised of the possibility of such damages.</p>
<p><strong>7. Disclaimer of Online Availability, Impressions, And Click-Throughs</strong></p>
<p>In addition to the other disclaimers and limitations discussed in this notice, there are no guarantees and no warranties regarding online availability, impressions, and click-through of www.BookMyInsurance.co.in, its web pages, and any material, information, links, or content presented on the web pages at www.BookMyInsurance.co.in. BookMyInsurance.co.in, its web pages, and any material, information, links, or content presented on the web pages at www.BookMyInsurance.co.in, may be unavailable for online access at anytime. Advertising sponsors and advertising,if any and if permitted, must be approved by BookMyInsurance before the posting of any advertising material, information, links, content, banners, and graphics on www.BookMyInsurance.co.in. BookMyInsurance reserves the right to accept or to reject any advertising sponsor or any advertising for any reason</p>]]></string>

	<string name="cancellrefund"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Cancellation &amp; Refund/Chargeback Terms and Conditions</strong></p>
<p>(a) Free look period Cancellation and Refund</p>
<p>As per the IRDAI rules and regulations, you have the right to cancel your insurance policy within 15(fifteen) days from the date of (online) receipt of insurance policy (referred to as &ldquo;Free look period&rdquo;) and refund of your premium amount shall be processed as per the applicable process and procedures followed by the insurer. This Free look facility can be availed only for Life and Health insurance policies, subject to certain other terms and conditions specified by IRDAI. We encourage all our customers to read the insurance policy document carefully and avail the free look facility in case the terms and conditions of the insurance policy document don&rsquo;t match your insurance requirements. Further, you understand that once you place a cancellation request within the Free look period, the policy gets cancelled and entire premium is refunded to you subject to deduction of (i) charges pertaining to medical tests conducted (ii) administrative and service cost like stamp duty etc. and; (iii )Charges for mortality for the period the policy was in force. Please note such deduction is at the sole discretion of the insurer.</p>
<p>All payments with respect to refunds as stated under this paragraph 1 shall be the sole responsibility of the insurer per the rules and regulations laid down by the IRDAI. You understand that BookMyInsurance has tied up with RBI authorized payment gateways to allow you to make online payments towards your insurance premium amount and is only acting as a mere facilitator and providing its assistance to its customers for speedy refunds.</p>
<p>(b) Chargebacks</p>
<p>You (cardholder) may dispute a transaction carried out through our Website and file a Charegback with your issuing bank for the reversal of that transaction. Chargeback allows transactions to be reversed by you under specified circumstances such as, on account of (i) alleged forgery of the card number / bank account or other details (ii) any charge/debit made on a card that has been listed as a hot listed card or otherwise listed on the card association (Visa, MasterCard, etc.) warning bulletins (iii) duplicate processing of the transaction; or (iv) for other reasons as per applicable rules and guidelines issued by RBI, card Associations, your card/payment instrument issuing bank etc. However, we reserve the right to reject a Chargeback, including but not limited to, under the following circumstances:</p>
<p>1. In the event your medical tests or underwriting is in process with your chosen insurer, not exceeding a period of 3 months from the date of your insurance policy application</p>
<p>2. In the event there is any delay caused on the part of the insurer in conducting medical tests or during the process of medical underwriting or issuance of insurance policy or any service provided by the insurer in connection with the insurance policy issuance, not exceeding a period of 3 months from the date of your insurance policy application</p>
<p>3. In case your insurance policy application is rejected by the insurer, post your medical test</p>
<p>Our Company shall not be liable to you, in any form or manner whatsoever, for any claims, disputes, proceedings which may arise in connection with Chargebacks initiated by you in the circumstances as specified under (a), (b) and (c) herein above.</p>
<p>2. Additional Terms and Conditions of proposal form (applicable for health insurance products only):</p>
<p>(i) You hereby declare, on your behalf and on behalf of all persons proposed to be insured, that the statements, answers and/ or particulars given by you are true and complete in all respects to the best of your knowledge and that you are authorized to propose on behalf of these other persons.</p>
<p>(ii) You understand that the information provided by you will form the basis of the insurance policy, is subject to the Board approved underwriting policy of the insurer and that the policy will come into force only after full payment of the premium chargeable.</p>
<p>(iii) You further declare that you will notify in writing any change occurring in the occupation or general health of the life to be insured/proposer after the proposal has been submitted but before communication of the risk acceptance by the insurance company.</p>
<p>(iv) You declare that you consent to the insurance company seeking medical information from any doctor or hospital who/which at any time has attended on the person to be insured/proposer or from any past or present employer concerning anything which affects the physical or mental health of the person to be insured/proposer and seeking information from any insurer to whom an application for insurance on the person to be insured/proposer has been made for the purpose of underwriting the proposal and/or claim settlement.</p>
<p>(v) You authorize the BookMyInsurance/insurance company to share information pertaining to your proposal including the medical records of the insured/ proposer for the sole purpose of underwriting the proposal and/or claims settlement and with any Governmental and/or Regulatory authority.</p>
<p>(vi) You consent to and authorize any of insurance company&rsquo;s authorized representatives not being direct employees of the company to seek medical information required for the purpose of policy issuance or claim settlement under this policy from any hospital/medical practitioner that you or any person proposed to be insured/insured has attended or may attend in future concerning any</p>
<p>disease or illness or injury.</p>
<p>(vii) You understand agree that (section 41 of Insurance Act):</p>
<p>a) No person shall allow or offer to allow, either directly or indirectly, as an inducement to any person to take out or renew or continue an insurance in respect of any kind of risk relating to lives or property in India, any rebate of the whole or part of the commission payable or any rebate of the premium shown on the policy, nor shall any person taking out or renewing or continuing a Policy accept any rebate, except such rebate as may be allowed in accordance with the published prospectuses or tables of the insurers.</p>
<p>b) Any person making default in complying with the provision of this section shall be liable for a penalty which may extend to ten lakh rupees.&rdquo;</p>
<p>3. Customer Due Diligence requirements (CDD)</p>
<p>You agree and acknowledge that for undertaking any financial transaction through the website, Our Company may undertake client/customer due diligence measurers and seek mandatory information required for KYC purpose which as a customer you are obliged to give, while facilitating your request of insurance requirements with the insurance company(ies), in accordance with applicable PMLA laws and rules. Our Company may obtain sufficient information to establish, to its satisfaction or the insurance company, the identity of each new customer, and the purpose of the intended nature of insurance relationship between you and the insurance company(ies). You agree and understand that you shall ensure that any payment towards insurance premium is remitted only through your bank account or from a joint bank account in which you are a joint holder. In the event, payment towards insurance premium is remitted through a bank account opened in the name of a third party(i.e. not being in your name), you agree and acknowledge that Our Company can undertake enhanced due diligence measures(including any documentation), to satisfy itself relating to customer due diligence requirements. You further agree and acknowledge that, in line with the requirements and obligations under the PMLA Act and rules, all refunds shall be processed by the insurance company(ies) through us to the bank account which was used to remit payment of insurance premium.</p>
<p>4. License Disclaimer</p>
<p>Nothing on any BookMyInsurance website shall be construed as conferring any license under any of BookMyInsurance\'s or any third party\'s intellectual property rights, whether by estoppel, implication, or otherwise.</p>
<p>5. Local Laws</p>
<p>BookMyInsurance controls and operates this Website from its headquarters in Bangalore, India and makes no representation that the materials on the website are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you use this Website from other locations, you are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws including but not limited to the export and import regulations of other countries. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, all marketing or promotional materials found on this Website are solely directed to individuals, companies or other entities located in India and comply with the laws prevailing for the time being in force in India. Disputes if any shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of Courts at Bangalore.</p>
<p>6. Limitation of Liability</p>
<p>You expressly understand and agree that BookMyInsurance and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors shall not be liable to you for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequntial or exemplary damages, including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses (even if BookMyInsurance has been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from use of the site, content or any related services. If, despite the limitation above, BookMyInsurance or its Affiliates are found liable for any loss or damage which arises out of or in any way connected with any of the occurrences described above, then the liability of BookMyInsurance and/or Its Affiliates will in no event exceed, in the aggregate, the greater of (a) the service fees you paid to BookMyInsurance in connection with such transaction(s) on this Site, or (b) Rupees One Hundred only (INR 100) The limitation of liability reflects the allocation of risk between the parties. The limitations specified in this section will survive and apply even if any limited remedy specified in these terms is found to have failed of its essential purpose. The limitations of liability provided in these terms inure to the benefit of BookMyInsurance, Its affiliates, and/or their respective service providers.</p>
<p>7. Indemnity</p>
<p>You agree to indemnify and hold BookMyInsurance (and its officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures, and employees) harmless from any and against any claims, causes of action, demands, recoveries, losses, damages, fines, penalties or other costs or expenses of any kind or nature, including reasonable attorneys\' fees, or arising out of or related to your breach of this ToU, your violation of any law or the rights of a third party, or your use of the Site.</p>
<p>8. Electronic Communication</p>
<p>When you use the Site or send emails to BookMyInsurance, you are communicating with BookMyInsurance electronically. You consent to receive communications from BookMyInsurance electronically. BookMyInsurance may communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the Site or by phone or usually available means of communication. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.</p>
<p>9. Site-Provided Email and Postings</p>
<p>The Site may provide users with the ability to send email messages to other users and non-users and to post messages on the Site. BookMyInsurance is under no obligation to review any messages, information or content ("Postings") posted on the Site by users and assumes no responsibility or liability relating to any such Postings. Notwithstanding the above, BookMyInsurance may from time to time monitor the Postings on the Site and may decline to accept and/or remove any email or Postings. You understand and agree that you shall not to use any functionality provided by the Site to post content or initiate communications that contain: (i) Any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including, but not limited to, any material which encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national or international law; (ii) Advertisements or solicitations of any kind; (iii) Impersonate others or provide any kind of false information; (iv) Personal information such as messages which state phone numbers, account numbers, addresses, or employer references.; (v) Messages by non-spokesperson employees of BookMyInsurance purporting to speak on behalf of BookMyInsurance or containing confidential information or expressing opinions concerning BookMyInsurance; (vi) Messages that offer unauthorized downloads of any copyrighted or private information; (vii) Multiple messages placed within individual folders by the same user restating the same point; (viii) Chain letters of any kind; or (ix) Identical (or substantially similar) messages to multiple recipients advertising any product or service, expressing a political or other similar message, or any other type of unsolicited commercial message. This prohibition includes but is not limited to a) Using BookMyInsurance to send messages to people who don\'t know you or who are unlikely to recognize you as a known contact; b) Using BookMyInsurance to connect to people who don\'t know you and then sending unsolicited promotional messages to those direct connections without their permission; and c) Sending messages to distribution lists, newsgroup aliases, or group aliases.</p>
<p>10. Links</p>
<p>The Site or third parties may provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. Because BookMyInsurance has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that BookMyInsurance is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that BookMyInsurance shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource.</p>
<p>11. Access to Password Protected/Secure Areas</p>
<p>Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of the Site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized individuals attempting to access these areas of the Site may be subject to prosecution.</p>
<p>12. Modification and Notification of Changes</p>
<p>BookMyInsurance reserves the right to make changes to the Site, related policies and agreements, this ToU and the Privacy Policy at any time. If BookMyInsurance makes a material modification to this ToU, it may notify you by: (i) displaying a prominent announcement above the text of this ToU or the Privacy Policy, as appropriate, for thirty (30) days, being deemed sufficient notification, of such changes. After notice of a modification to the ToU or the Privacy Policy has been posted for 30 days, the notice will be removed. If you have not used the Site for more than 30 days, you should check the ToU and/or Privacy Policy prior to any further use of the Site. Should you wish to terminate your account due to a modification to the TOU or the Privacy Policy, you may do so by sending an email with the subject line "Termination" to the following email address: support@BookMyInsurance.co.in. If you choose to continue using the Site, you agree that by doing so you will be deemed to accept the new ToU or Privacy Policy, as relevant.</p>
<p>13. Trademarks</p>
<p>The trademarks, logos and service marks ("Marks") displayed on the Site are the property of BookMyInsurance/its parent company and other associated parties and service providers. Users are prohibited from using any Marks for any purpose including, but not limited to use as metatags on other pages or sites on the World Wide Web without the written permission of BookMyInsurance or such third party which may own the Marks. All information and content including any software programs available on or through the Site ("Content") is protected by copyright. Users are prohibited from modifying, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, publishing, selling, licensing, creating derivative works or using any Content available on or through the Site for commercial or public purposes.</p>
<p>14. Survival of Terms After Agreement Ends</p>
<p>Notwithstanding any other provisions of this ToU, or any general legal principles to the contrary, any provision of this ToU that imposes or contemplates continuing obligations on a party will survive the expiration or termination of this ToU.</p>
<p>15. General</p>
<p>If any of these conditions are deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, the parties agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties&rsquo; intentions as reflected in the provision, and the unenforceable condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition. Headings are for reference purposes only and do not limit the scope or extent of such section. This ToU and the relationship between you and BookMyInsurance will be governed by the laws of the India without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and BookMyInsurance agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in Bangalore jurisdiction with respect to any legal proceedings that may arise in connection with this ToU. The failure of BookMyInsurance to act with respect to a breach by you or others does not waive its right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches. BookMyInsurance does not guarantee it will take action against all breaches of this ToU. Except as otherwise expressly provided in this ToU, there shall be no third-party beneficiaries to this ToU. This ToU constitutes the entire agreement between you and BookMyInsurance and governs your use of the Site, superseding any prior agreements between you and BookMyInsurance with respect to the Site.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p>BookMyInsurance intends to provide clear and unbiased information about insurance products and services. The information and data are generic in nature. Our efforts are to offer unbiased, accurate and responsible data to the best of our ability. We are however, in no manner or form responsible for any discrepancies in the data published on our website.</p>
<p>There is no intention or purpose of violating any intellectual property or ancillary rights. All information provided on the portal BookMyInsurance is subject to it&rsquo;s discretion and is likely to change without any notice. Though, any changes in public utility will be communicated on our portal.</p>
<p>Although we have tried to maintain high standards in quality, clarity and accuracy of the material posted on the portal. BookMyInsurance is not legally responsible for the same in any manner what so ever.</p>
<p>Employees, partners and associated staff of BookMyInsurance are not accountable for any loss, harm or damage that occurs or may occur or arise from the usage of information from the portal. Customers are advised to use their own discretion in such matters.</p>
<p>It is important to understand that insurance is a subject matter of solicitation and market risks. It is the responsibility of the customer to understand the limitations of insurance policies and the risks involved, and under no circumstance, form or manner, do we take any liability in such cases.We also recommend you to please read the subject and offer documents carefully. The information provided on the portal is for financial and insurance purposes.</p>
<p>It is a mutual understanding between us and the customers that their association with the portal will be at the customer\'s sole discretion and risk.</p>
<p>Visitors to this website/portal and every third party is hereby informed that the owners of this website/portal, viz., Rajachan Advisors Private Limited, are not the agents, corporate agents, related party or intermediaries of the insurers, whose products are dealt with in this website/portal. They are also not the sub-agents or sub-intermediaries of the agents and intermediaries of the respective insurers. Though endeavour is made to make correct policy/product comparisons, quotes, features, etc., based on the information provided by the insurers, it is made abundantly clear that Rajachan Advisors Private Limited, its directors, shareholders, officers and employees and BookMyInsurance.co.in are in no way responsible to or liable for any one for his/her investment decision, and every prospect/ investor/policyholder shall be solely responsible for the consequences of his/her decision.</p>]]></string>
	<string name="refunfcancellation"><![CDATA[Refund & Cancellation]]></string>
</resources>
